[folk music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
ACROBATIC SHOW
FEMALE KNIFE THROWER
[man 1] Whoa!
[man 1 laughs]
That's not what we wanna see!
MANRAKU TROUPE
-[man 1] That's some skill.
-[man 2 whoops]
Come on, no one cares
for knife-throwing at this day and age.
[man 2] With a pretty face like that,
why don't you just lose that kimono
and sing us a song?
-[man 3] Damn right!
-[man 1] Show us your beautiful fair skin!
-[man 2] Yeah!
-[man 1] Pretty please!
[crowd laughing]
[grunts]
-[brooding music playing]
-[breathing heavily]
-Oh wow.
-[gasping]
CIVILIZATION AND ENLIGHTENMENT
-[man 1] Look at that!
-[crowd laughing]
-[man 2] Lose the kimono and do it again.
-[man 3] Impressive. A lot of talent.
[boy 1] I want one!
-[boy 2] Me too.
-Come on then.
-I can't keep doing this forever.
-I agree.
-He was here.
-[woman] Can't we rest just this once?
-I don't want to hear you complaining.
-I'm so stressed.
-[sighs] Creep.
-Iroha.
Why not part with those blades
and start selling your body instead?
I certainly wouldn't mind paying for it.
[indistinct background chatter]
What?
What are you glaring at me for? Huh?
You didn't forget
who took you in, did you?
Hey.
[man scoffs]
[insects chirping]
You're alive, huh?
I'm glad.
[chuckles softly] I never thought
you'd be a traveling performer.
I could hardly recognize you.
I'm surprised you didn't lose your temper.
I bet the old Iroha would've put them
all in their graves. [laughs]
I'm already used to it.
How have you been?
Good.
I've been out pulling a rickshaw
every day to feed my wife and daughter.
I see. You have a family now, then.
[Sansuke] Yeah. What about you?
What've you been doing
since you left the mountain?
What I could.
I traveled a lot,
always trying to hide from Gentosai.
Hm.
How's everybody?
Fugoro and Shichiya
were killed by Gentosai.
[unsettling music playing]
He's been searching
for the surviving disciples of our school.
[breathing shakily]
[Sansuke] Iroha.
If it goes on like this,
we'll definitely be killed too.
I found Shikura and Jinroku
and talked them into it.
They are joining me very soon.
Joining you? What do you mean by that?
We'll lure Gentosai into this
and finish him off ourselves.
We'll never kill him
unless we strike together as siblings.
Iroha.
You know this is our fate as a family.
[breath trembling]
[unsettling music fades]
[birds chirping]
[footsteps approaching]
[door opens]
Sorry for the wait. [chuckles]
-And now…
-[claps]
…to uncover the true purpose
of this Kodoku,
enters Kyojin, the great strategist--
Can you just get to the point already?
The plan has two parts.
For the first experiment,
we'll hand someone over to the authorities
with their tag still around their neck.
[drum beating]
They won't be able to make it
to Tokyo if they're incarcerated.
It should count as a withdrawal.
As of now,
I still have no idea what they would do
to a contestant who's in jail.
So you plan to find out if the rules
still count even in jail, right?
[Kyojin] Correct.
Are they willing to go against the police
to silence a defeated contestant,
or is that taking it a step too far,
even for those lunatics?
This will show us how far the mastermind
is willing to take this Kodoku.
For the second experiment,
we'll figure out where all
of the dead bodies disappear to.
-Disappear?
-[Kyojin] Mm-hmm.
With all these folks traveling
on the Tokaido Road,
murdering each other left and right,
it wouldn't be strange to see a dead body
or two along the way, and yet we don't.
What does that tell you?
That the bodies are taken
and hidden out of sight.
Correct once again.
By the way, they're always watching us.
I'm sure you've all realized that
by now, haven't you?
Well, they wouldn't follow us
inside this room, at least.
But rest assured, they are watching us.
So they're even cleaning up the corpses?
That's quite the undertaking, isn't it?
Indeed. They're likely
hauling them off somewhere, hm?
The conclusion here?
They have concealed locations
and the means to secretly haul hundreds
of dead bodies from all the towns.
Splendid answer.
If we find out
where the dead bodies are being hidden,
we might figure out a little more
about the people behind this.
What do you think?
It seems like a nice plan, right?
Right. So where do we begin?
First off, we go out there
and find our lucky volunteer.
[dramatic music playing]
Why would the zaibatsu
purchase over 100 rifles
and make the shizoku kill one another?
Since the Meiji era began,
they've likely been profiting
off government contracts.
[hits desk]
What on earth do they gain
from doing a thing like this?
[brooding music playing]
They're all betting, huh?
Just so all those fools
will kill one another?
Isn't there a chance
this is their actual purpose?
[Okubo] Hatred for the former samurai?
I'm sure it's no small burden,
bearing the shizoku's
relentless plundering.
There's one more thing I've learned.
I checked with the zaibatsu,
and we've confirmed
that these four individuals have been
on an extended leave since a week ago.
No one knows where they went.
None of them were home.
-Find them as soon as you can.
-[Kawaji] Yes, sir.
[man] Lord Okubo.
I mean no disrespect,
but meddling with the zaibatsu
could bring repercussions to our economy.
[Kawaji] Mr. Nagase.
If they are truly behind this,
then this is treason against the state.
We must deal with this
as soon as possible.
-[Okubo] Kawaji.
-Sir.
Bring the four of them here at once.
Our efforts to find them
are already underway, sir.
-I'll resume my work on the telegrams.
-[Okubo] Good.
[door opens]
-[door closes]
-[exhales]
[seagulls calling]
KUWANA-JUKU
[woman] Have a look, have a taste!
Kuwana's famous grilled clams!
Get yours while they're hot!
We've got horse mackerel, squid,
clams and fine sake to wash it down!
Been on the road a while, haven't you?
How about a short break
before you carry on?
Okay, right this way!
-Customers coming in!
-[customers speaking indistinctly]
[woman] Welcome!
A group of four coming in!
[man 1] Oh no!
-Argh, I can't get it right.
-[man 2] Shut up. You're distracting me.
-[man 3 laughs]
-[man 4 sighs]
Come on in!
We have a table available in the back.
We'll take some tea
and hotchpotch, please.
Of course.
Tea and four bowls of hotchpotch!
[man 5] All right!
[woman] All right. One bowl of mixed rice
and grilled squid, people.
Look at that one.
Didn't even bother to hide his tag.
That's quite some confidence.
They're participants too.
-Hey. Can't you see it's empty?
-[Iroha] I saw them at Tenryuji.
-Hmm?
-I'm sorry. Let me do this.
Who's our lucky volunteer?
-[man 6] What the hell is wrong with you?
-[man 7] I'm sorry!
You're a deadweight.
What the hell is your problem?
-I'm really sorry! I'm sorry!
-[man 6] Shut up!
I'm sorry, sir.
Let's go with
whoever leaves this teahouse first.
[man 8 laughs]
-[footsteps approaching]
-That won't be necessary.
[customers fall silent]
[foreboding music playing]
[Kyojin] Who the hell are you?
More than one of you I guess, huh?
[man 8] "More than one?"
Hmm… Yes, indeed. I would say we are.
Hm?
[Kyojin] Oh.
I figured most of the participants
would pass right by this teahouse,
so I took the liberty
of arranging
a delightful little trap here.
I thought talking to outsiders was
a violation of the rules, right?
But hiring them,
without revealing the details, is not.
Aren't you the strategist?
[whispers] It's not too bad.
As for the girls…
Oh, you might as well
enjoy yourselves, boys.
[laughing]
[foreboding music intensifies]
All right. I'll leave you to it.
[indistinct chatter]
YOKKAICHI-SHUKU
[exhales]
[Kanjiya] Lower-intermediate.
Beginner.
Hmm?
Pre-intermediate.
[chuckles softly]
Hey.
You're a contestant, aren't you?
I'm looking for a swordsman
traveling with a girl.
Have you seen anyone like that?
[ominous music playing]
No.
[scoffs]
How could I have let them slip
through my fingers the other night?
A bow, huh?
You're so far away.
Where's the fun in killing someone
if you can't look 'em in the eye?
No different from guns, is it?
This is an instrument
for tributes and offerings to the gods.
Nothing like a gun.
-[grunts]
-[yelps]
[dramatic music playing]
[man 1 screaming, whimpering]
[Kanjiya laughs]
To hell with all your gods.
What nonsense.
[woman] Darling!
[sobbing] No! Stay with me, darling.
Don't leave me like this, darling! No!
-[groans]
-[villagers gasping]
If gods truly existed,
do you think
this would be the state of the world?
Huh. Nice.
[villagers screaming]
Let's have fun.
[man 2] He's coming! He's coming!
Die, you rats!
-[groaning]
-Oh.
Go get the girls!
Get them first!
Get me their tags,
and I'll pay thrice the price!
-[yelling]
-[grunting]
[dramatic music continues]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[straining]
Outta the way!
[grunting]
This trap isn't working out for you.
-[screams]
-[gasping]
Who are these people?
You told us this would be easy!
[indistinct shouting]
[yells]
[straining]
-[yells]
-[shrieks]
[breathing shakily]
[groaning]
[invigorating music playing]
[yells]
[shrieking]
-[Iroha grunting]
-[thumping]
Go! Hurry up! Go get them!
-[yelling]
-[groaning]
-[grunting]
-[screams]
-[glass smashing]
-[grunting]
[yelling]
[groaning]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[man shrieks]
[yells, groans]
[screams]
[woman shrieks]
[screaming]
-Let go! Let go!
-[yells]
-[grunts]
-[coughing]
[whimpering]
-[villagers screaming]
-[dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
Help! Someone warn the police!
-[screams]
-[Kanjiya grunting]
-[shrieks]
-[body thuds]
[groaning, breathing heavily]
[exhales]
-[grunting]
-[screaming]
[yelps]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[groaning]
It's an offering for the gods, am I right?
[Kanjiya grunting]
[shrieking]
-[Sakura] That's enough!
-[dramatic music fades]
[footsteps approaching]
Do I know you from somewhere?
The police have been notified.
They're coming this way.
[Kanjiya laughs] Yeah, so what?
The hosts have high expectations
of the two of you.
Your failure would dull the thrill.
You think I'll get caught?
I could kill you right here and now.
Do you realize that?
Suit yourself.
If you think you can win
against this many rifles.
[dramatic sting]
[Kanjiya] This is no fun.
-[guns withdrawing]
-[exhales]
[Sakura] The times have changed.
The samurai have no place in this world.
You suffered through the war,
and yet what came after was worse,
[somber music playing]
Wasn't it, Kanjiya Bukotsu?
Oh, my business is not your concern.
-[seagulls calling]
-[customers whimpering, breathing shakily]
All right. Which one of you, huh?
Wait.
What sort of scheme are you forcing on us?
We'll hand one of you over to the police,
tag still round your neck.
What?
Uh, wait. I mean, if you do that--
Either the Kodoku squad will kill you,
or the police will protect you.
There's no telling which.
What?
What about the other one of us?
We'll be taking their tag.
That's it, game over.
[gasps]
[struggling] Hand me over to the police!
Please pick me to go!
Huh?
I'm doing it, not you.
Shut up and let me do it!
[laughing nervously]
Well, this is the end
of the line for you, I'm afraid.
[man 1 cackles]
Please. I'll do anything.
Anything, please, I beg you!
[Kyojin] Just accept it.
You've killed your share
of contestants yourself, haven't you?
[man 2] I've never killed anyone. I swear!
Even at Tenryuji, I just stole the tags
from the men who died.
-[Kyojin] I'm not interested in your lies.
-[man 2] I'm not lying!
I was… threatened into it.
He said I'd stay alive if I did this.
-Don't you lie!
-[man 2 groans]
-[man 1 chuckles]
-[sobbing]
Our family's poor.
I joined to help my father
with his business failures.
I never imagined…
we'd have to kill each other.
[sniffs]
But I simply cannot do it.
[somber music playing]
I beg you not to kill me.
Don't do it.
Don't let it end like this, please!
[Kyojin] You think he's telling the truth?
All right. You win.
[breathing shakily]
But in return,
you'll be at my side lending a hand.
Thank you. Oh, thank you.
Thank you very much!
Huh?
Hey, wait a minute.
-Can I be at your side lending a ha--
-All right, Shujiro.
You find out where
they're taking the bodies.
[Saga] All right.
[Kyojin] Oh, by the way, Iroha.
-[curious music playing]
-Here you go.
-[Iroha] What's this?
-[Kyojin] It's a smoke ball.
What am I going to do with this?
Just keep it at hand.
I'll have the police sent here.
Take advantage of the ruckus to get past
the Kodoku guards keeping watch.
Well… Ah!
All right, let's go. The plan is launched.
[man 1 breathing shakily]
[curious music fades]
[knocking]
Come in.
The analysis is complete.
It's exactly as you suspected, sir.
They rely on telegrams
for their communication.
DOMESTIC TELEGRAM RECORD
Since May 5th,
when we received reports from Tenryuji,
there's been
a sudden increase in correspondence.
NUMBER OF TELEGRAMS
MAY 5TH: 156
[Okubo] Hmm.
What else?
We couldn't decipher the messages.
They're using some sort of code.
However,
we managed to find out
where these telegrams originated.
Go on.
-Show him.
-Yes, sir.
[ominous music playing]
It's near the southern side of Mount Fuji.
As you can see,
the map suggests there's nothing there.
MOUNT FUJI
SHIZUOKA TELEGRAPH OFFICE
That means their headquarters are there.
Kawaji, head there now.
Let us proceed.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[man 1] "Clash Between Shizoku
in Yokkaichi City on the Tokaido Road."
[mechanical clicking]
[laughing]
[ominous music continues]
[man 2] Gentlemen.
What is it?
Looks like the state is taking action.
What?
Nothing to be worried about.
They can't reach us here.
They couldn't possibly find us.
Even if they did,
we're protected by a guardian god.
[Morosawa chuckles]
Oh. [chuckles] That's right.
That's a fair point, my friend.
-[laughing]
-Well said.
[indistinct chatter]
Iroha-san.
Thank you for saving me earlier.
I was wondering,
at what age did you start your training?
All of us at Kyohachi-ryu
were abandoned as kids.
We don't know our real ages.
Were there other girls there?
Other than yourself?
No.
I was so young
and the weakest of all.
You were the weakest?
It was a long time ago.
I want to be as strong as you are.
Can you share some advice?
[mellow music playing]
I wouldn't worry yourself with it.
Strength won't help you win.
No matter how skilled you become,
happiness remains out of reach.
[footsteps above]
-He's here.
-[breathing heavily]
[foreboding music playing]
[man groaning] Ow!
Hey, that hurts. Hey.
Hey, a little gentleness, please! Argh!
-Oh, sir.
-There was a murder at the teahouse.
-He's the main suspect.
-[man] No, no, no!
We'll be holding him in jail.
-Yes, sir.
-Let's go!
-[whimpering]
-[grunting]
Ah, I can't wait to see what happens next.
-[man] Please, don't!
-Shut up!
POLICE BRANCH STATION
[eerie music playing]
-[shrieking]
-[straining]
You stay quiet in here.
We'll interrogate you later.
[man] Hey! Wait.
Listen. Listen! [breathing shakily]
Where's the guard?
Shouldn't there be a guard here?
What's wrong, huh?
Scared of spirits, are you?
[laughing] Oh, no way. Of course not.
Oh hey! Wait! Wait! Hey! Don't!
Hey! Don't leave me alone!
[suspenseful music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Futaba breathing shakily]
[Iroha] Let's go.
Police Bureau.
The chief knows we're coming.
Oh.
Looks like our bait worked, huh?
-Huh?
-What's your name, kiddo?
Uh, Sayama Shinnosuke, sir.
Shinnosuke, hold these for me.
Huh?
Uh, wait.
[wheels rolling]
Seventeen past two, 108, Saga Shujiro.
[thudding]
We're here to interrogate the suspect
who was just detained.
Yes, sir. Uh, he's in the basement.
I'll show you the way. Ah.
Hello, sir.
Hello.
I'll join them for the interrogation.
[guard] Yes, sir.
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[indistinct chatter]
[ominous music playing]
Wait a second, this is…
108, Saga Shujiro was eliminated
at 2:17 p.m. in Kuwana.
[suspenseful music playing]
[doors close]
[suspenseful music fades]
[papers rustling]
[screams]
-[choking]
-[grunting]
-[breathing heavily]
-[gurgles]
MITSUI BANK
RECORD OF ALL TRANSACTIONS
MITSUI BANK OPENING LOAN DEPOSIT
MITSUI BANK GUIDELINES
FOR ESTIMATING WRITE-OFFS
MITSUI BANK
INTERNAL RULES
[ominous music playing]
[gasps]
Wait, is this…
MITSUI BANK
[Iroha] A bank.
[ominous music continues]
I know that man.
[ominous music fades]
[water dripping]
[sighs]
[door opens]
[footsteps approaching]
[breath trembling]
Here to question me?
Listen to me.
I didn't kill anyone, all right?
It's complex, but I can explain.
Some unknown devils
are making us slaughter each other.
They're killing whoever tries to escape.
I need someone to guard me down here.
-Please! Keep those madmen away from me.
-[tense music playing]
Wait.
Wait, no! Wait, wait!
[body thuds]
[tense music fades]
[sighs]
[tense music resumes]
[door closes]
[tense music fades]
[breathing heavily]
-[Sakura] So 108's body is here?
-[man] Yes, sir.
[doors closing]
[exhales]
[suspenseful music playing]
It seems like
a mouse has made its way inside.
[sighs]
[man] And who might you be?
Fourth Division. The name's Takayama.
I don't remember any
of my subordinates going by that name.
Oh, so you're Fourth Division too.
Mm.
Best answer you could find…
[chuckles softly]
…Tsuge Kyojin?
[suspenseful music continues]
You forgot to plan an escape route, huh?
Come out.
No use dragging this out any longer…
Saga Kokushu.
[suspenseful music fades]
[breathing heavily]
Nakamura Hanjiro.
I go by the name of Sakura now.
When I saw you kill Ando
at Tenryuji Temple,
I had my suspicions.
I have been secretly rooting for you.
Back then, I was sure you were dead.
[men shouting]
Strange how that works.
Life is surprising.
For as long as I can remember,
I wanted to be just like you, you know.
Just tell me one thing.
What are you all hoping to achieve?
I cannot answer that, I'm afraid.
But when old comrades reunite,
they either drink together…
or they fight.
-[foreboding music playing]
-[sword unsheathing]
It's one or the other.
[sheath clatters]
[exhales]
[foreboding music intensifies]
[foreboding music ends]
[exhales]
[footsteps approaching]
Our analysis, sir.
All of the coded telegrams were sent
to or from this location,
the Nihonbashi Telegraph Office.
From there,
we managed to track down
the recipient of the telegrams
and pinpoint their location.
It's not what we expected.
What is it?
The final destination
of these telegrams was…
the Police Bureau, our own.
[dramatic music playing]
Gentlemen. Sorry to keep you waiting.
We're glad you're here, sir.
I'm sure you were very busy
from overseeing all this, right?
-Mmm.
-[laughing]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[foreboding music playing]
[sighs]
Lord Okubo,
I don't mean
to speak out of turn, but I must ask…
[Okubo sighs]
Go ahead.
Are you certain that we can trust Kawaji?
Once again, thank you all for being here
and for your continued support.
It's all for the good of this country.
-Whatever you need, don't hesitate to ask.
-[Kawaji] Thank you very much.
[dramatic music playing]
This is a critical endeavor.
The samurai are like ghosts,
and we must eradicate them at all costs.
So, gentlemen,
let's see this mission through together…
[dramatic music continues]
…for the sake of our country's tomorrow.
[clapping]
[grunts]
70 REMAINING
[ambient music playing]
[music fades]